<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Surmoni Client</string>
    <string name="title_streamer">Streamer</string>
    <string name="title_player">Player</string>
    <string name="streaming_start">Start</string>
    <string name="streaming_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="sign_up">SGIN UP</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="agree_to_our_terms_and_condition">Agree to our terms and Condition</string>
    <string name="already_have_any_account">Already have any Account ?</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior" translatable="false">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="help_desc"><b>Help : </b>Before you get started you need two android devices.
    Download Surmoni server application in one device and download Surmoni client app in other device.
    Signup on client app with email and password.After initial setup get your client id from client id section.
        This client id will be used to register server with your client application.Open your server application and
    register your client id.Now client application will get bound to that server and will be able to get updates and monitorings of
    temperature, humidity, motion detection etc.It will notify you about ur server status.In case of crash restart server and client applications again.You can contact us if help needed.
        \n\n<b>Live Stream Setup : </b> To use Live Stream feature you need to register yourself on firekast.io and need to setup storage project for your videos.After
        that copy your private-key from settings and enter it in respected field(Live Stream->private-key field or Live Stream->edit key button).
        \n\n<b>How to use Live Stream : </b> <i>First Click START to initialize streaming on Server and after 60 secs(1 minute or on slow internet wait for 5 minutes) or more Click PLAY to watch Stream.After watching Click STOP to stop streaming on Server.</i>.
        \n\n<b>Settings : </b> <i>After changing camera settings restart client and server applications.</i>
        \n\n<b>Note : </b> <i>Only use one server application with only one application client otherwise applications will not
            work and will keep on stopping.</i></string>

    <array name="menu_items">
        <item>@drawable/fire</item>
        <item>@drawable/drop</item>
        <item>@drawable/bino</item>
        <item>@drawable/shoes</item>
        <item>@drawable/battery</item>
        <item>@drawable/client_id_icon</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="menu_item_desc">
        <item>This shows current temperature in celcius.</item>
        <item>Select this shows current humidity in percentage.</item>
        <item>Select this option is for live streaming.</item>
        <item>Select this option is for live motion detection.</item>
        <item>Select this option is for Electrical status of server.</item>
        <item>Select this option is for help.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="menus">
        <item>Temperature</item>
        <item>Humidity</item>
        <item>Live Stream</item>
        <item>Motion Detection</item>
        <item>Electrical Status</item>
        <item>Client ID</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
